A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of Civilian Defense, 1940-1945.
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Correspondence, 1942-1945., Extent: 10.15 cubic feet (29 boxes). (Box 1-29)
  - Correspondence, 1943-1945.
    - Brooks, Julian A. (American Red Cross, Eastern Area), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Brooks, J. Murray (Mathews County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Brown, Aretha B. (Culpeper County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Brown, Charles E. (York County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Buc-Byk - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Buchanan, A. C., Judge (Tazewell County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Budwesky, Carl (Alexandria CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Buford, J. D., Rev. (Nelson County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Burgess, L. J. (Princess Anne CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Burnley, Seth (Charlottesville CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Butts, H. U., Mrs. (Roanoke County CDC - Civilian Mobilization), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Burrough, S. L. (Essex County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Cal-Caw - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Caffee, Emma S. (Newport News CDC - Civilian Mobilization), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Call, Norman (R. F. and P Railroad), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Caldwell, W. H. (Chesterfield County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Campbell, J. Owen (Botetourt County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Campbell, Walker E. (Floyd County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Cappon, Lester J., Dr. (World War II History Commission), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Caravati, Henry L. (Office of Price Administration), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Carper, W. H. (Culpeper County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Carpenter, H. D. (Williamsburg CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Carrier, Lester R. (Covington CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Carruthers, E. J., Maj. (Virginia District, Third Service Command - Military Intelligence), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Carson, A. L., Jr., Dr. (Dept. of Health), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Carter, Allen J. (American Red Cross), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Carter, Henry S. (Bishop CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Carter, J. S. (Pittsylvania County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Carter, W. H. (Amherst County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Cassell, S. K. (Agricultural Adjustment Agency), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Causey, J. C. (Suffolk CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Cha-Chu - Miscellaneous 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Chapman, W. Frank (Roanoke County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Chippewa Mills, Inc., 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Chiles, John, Dr. (Staunton CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Cia-Cly, 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Clapp, Roger F. (Richmond Army Service Forces Depot), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Clark, W. Blair (Patrick County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Cleek, Ernest S. (Bath County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Clemens, M. A. (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Clifford, William H., Col. (Loudoun County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Closson, George F. (Warwick County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Coc-Cox - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Cogbill, M. A. (Chesterfield County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Coleman, Frank (King George County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Coley, Grady (Scott County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Colonna, George B. (Elizabeth City County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Comer, George F. (Saltville CDC - Civilian Mobilization), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Commanding Officers, 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Connelly, L. B., Jr. (Russell County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Conway, G. F. (Caroline County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Cooke, J. Branham (Civilian Air Raid Warning Chief), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Cooper, Peter D. (Celco Plant), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Copenhaver, Marvin (Marion Hardware and Supply/OPA), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Cox, Jessie (Rappahannock County CDC - Civilian Mobilization), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Cooley, A. E. (Carroll County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Cra-Cru - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Craig, Daley (Augusta County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Creighton, Martha (State Nutrition Committee), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Crockett, C. Lucien (Norfolk and Western Railroad), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Crump, Sheppard, Col. (State Property Officer), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Cromwell, Frances, Miss (Child Care Committee), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Cub-Cuw - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Dar-Dew - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Daniel, James R. V. (American Red Cross), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Darden, Colgate W. (Governor of Virginia), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Davis, A. M. (Buena Vista CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Davis, Edith D. (Hospital Association of Roanoke), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Davis, J. J., Hon. (South Norfolk CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Davis, Miller, Capt. (Norfolk Air Defense Wing), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Day, Sidney C. (Comptroller's Office), 1943-1945. (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Deary, Floyd T. (Princess Anne County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - DeJarnette, Edmund T. (Hanover County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Denison, George L. (Hotel Roanoke), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Devine, Thomas (U. S. Office of Civilian Defense - Division of Federal-State Cooperation), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Dib-Diz - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Dickenson, W. A. (Cape Charles CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Dietrick, L. B. (Extension Service - V.P.I.), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Dillon, L. F. (Virginia Beach CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Dob-Dow - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Dobbs, J. R., Lt. (Wing CARW - Norfolk Air Defense), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Dodge, Inc., 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Doherty, Richard P. (Massachusetts Committee on Public Safety), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Donnell, A. T. (West Point CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Doolittle, Clifford (Giles County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Doss, J. S. (Craig County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Dotson, H. L., Capt. (Third Service Command), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Dower, R. S., Hon. (Radford CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Dra-Duz - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Drake, Grace (Warwick County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Dreyfuss, Leonard (East Coast Conference of State Defense Directors), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Dudley, W. H. (Lancaster County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Dugger, E. F. (Newport News Waterworks Commission), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Duling, D. W., Lt. (Richmond CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Dunn, A. E. (Virginia Electric and Power Company), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Dura Products Manufacturing Company, 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Duval, Harry (Office of Price Administration - Richmond District), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - E - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Eberwine, V. G. (Nansemond County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Eddins, R. C. (Blackstone CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Edmonds, James E., Maj. Gen. (Camp Lee), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Elder, D. Lane, Hon. (Hopewell CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Elderdice, Hugh L., Lt. Col. (Third Service Command), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Ellett, Tazewell (Henrico County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Elliott, H. M. (Washington County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Elliott, W. Glenn, Lt. Col. (Aircraft Warning Service), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Elliott, W. W. (Virginia Beach CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Ellis, E. F., Capt. (Wing CARW - Norfolk Air Base), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Ely, Robert B. (Lee County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Eskridge, A. T., Hon. (Mayor of Pulaski), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Eure, Arthur B. (State Highway Dept.), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Ewald, W. G. (Maryland Council of Defense), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Fab-Few - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Fair, Amalie S., Mrs. (Federal Works Agency), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Farley, J. W., Hon. (Massachusetts Committee on Public Safety), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Farnum, F. H., Col. (Maine Civilian Defense Council), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Farrar, Norman E. (Pamplin CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Fear, James D. (Conserve Critical Resources Committee), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Fendall, T. M. (Loudoun County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Ferguson, H. C., Capt. (Roanoke Superintendent of Police), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Fia-Fiz - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Fields, M. A. (Central High School - Goochland County), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Fitzgerald, E. G. (Campbell County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Fitzpatrick, W. C., Hon. (Farmville CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Fla-Fly - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Fletcher, Marshall P., Maj. (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Flood, Joel W., Mrs. (Appomattox County CDC - Civilian Mobilization), 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Fob-Foy - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Fra-Fuq - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Frailey, Thomas J., Lt. Col. (U.S. Office of Civilian Defense), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - France, Robert (Maryland Council of Defense), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Francis, J. L. (Sussex County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Franklin, C. S., Dr. (Charles City County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Franklin, W. A., Dr. (West Point CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Free, Elmer D. (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Freeman, Mallory (WRNL), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Freeman, Phillip, Mrs. (Sussex County CDC - Civilian Mobilization), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Fuller, Charles I. (Wise County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Funk, M. C. (Appalachian Electric Power Company), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Furlong, W. H. (Dupont), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Gab-Gay - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Gallehon, James H. (Bland County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Gamble, Robert H. (Northampton County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Garber, Walter E. (King William County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Gardner, J. A. (Appalachia CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Gardner, W. E. (Danville CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Garrett, James N. (Norfolk County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Garvin, J. E. (Altavista Mills), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Gea-Giw - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Geddy, Vernon M. (Williamsburg CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Geoghegan, Charles E. (Mecklenburg County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - George Mason Hotel, 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Gibson, C. Huntley (America Tobacco Company), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Gibson, Lanhorne, Lt. Comm. (Naval Intelligence Office), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Gibson, Paul (Richmond CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Gillard, W. H. (Prince George County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Gillespie, John W. (Tazewell County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Gilliland, Mary H. (Halifax County CDC - Civilian Mobilization), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Gilmer, T. A. (Russell County CDC - Civilian Mobilization), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Gilmer, W. B. (Louisa County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Gilmer, H. G. (Comptroller of Virginia), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Gla-Gow - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Glass, E. S. (Norfolk and Western Railway), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Glover, J. Frank (U.S. Office of Civilian Defense), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Goodwin, Bernard C. (Office of Price Administration), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Gra-Gwy - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Grahame, Emmette V. (Office of War Information), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Grant, S. Lee (Winchester CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Gray, Marvin L. (Sussex County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Greathead, McCarrell, Mrs. (Richmond CDC - Civilian Mobilization), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Greenstein, Harry (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Greer, Mary Carr (Albemarle County Training School), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Griffin, H. E. (Buckingham County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Griffith, Alfred H. (Buena Vista CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Groth, W. L. (Dept. of State Police), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Grubert, William A. (Mayor of Staunton), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Guyer, R. Sanford (WBTM), 1943-1945. (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Haa-Haz - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Hackler, J. S. (Martinsville CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Haden, H. A. (Albemarle County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Hahman, W. F. (Dept. of the Interior), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Hairston, William H. (Martinsville CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Hall, Channing M. (Williamsburg CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Hall, Henry C., Lt. (King and Queen County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Hall, Herbert C. (King and Queen County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Hall, John Hopkins (Dept. of Labor), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Hall, Stanley H. (Portsmouth CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Hall, W. L. (Staunton CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Hankins, May O., Mrs. (Commissioner of Public Welfare), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Hanrahan, Edward M., Mrs. (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Hanrahan, Frank C. (Arlington County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Hansel, Seybert (Highland County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Hardiman, L. J., Jr. (Norfolk CDC - Civilian Mobilization), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Hardy, Rives (Blackstone CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Harper, Charles H. (Winchester CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Harrison, E. E. (New Kent County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Harrison, Sydney M., Lt. Col. (U.S. Office of Civilian Defense), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Harper, E. C., Dr. (Emergency Medical Service), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Harris, Berry (Waynesboro CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Harris, George A., Jr. (Lunenburg County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Harris, H., Maj. (Hampton CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Hart, R. W. B. (Lynchburg CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Hartman, C. N. (Warwick County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Harwood, Hugh C. (Harwood Construction Company), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Harwood, T. P. (Crewe CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Haskell, William N., Lt. (Save the Children Federation), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Hassinger, L. C. (Bristol CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Hastings, E. M. (Richmond-Fredericksburg-Potomac Telephone Company), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Hatchett, Joseph M. (Petersburg CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Havens, Wilbur M. (WMGB), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Hays, James M., Jr. (State Corporation Commission), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Hayes, W. W., Prof. (Bristol CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Hayworth, Donald (Dept. of the Interior), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Hea-Hit - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Heald, Wistar M. (Mead Corporation), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Hedderly, J. Edgar (Office of Price Administration), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Heller, G. E. (Virginia Office of Civilian Defense), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Henderson, Ruth, Miss (State Dept. of Education), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Henninger, L. L. (U. S. Office of Civilian Defense), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Herbert, W. G., Capt. (Richmond CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Herrmann, A. H. (Virginia Electric and Power Company), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Hill, William Earl (Brunswick County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Hinckley, John A. (Fauquier County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Hoa-Hoz - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Hobeck, Clarence (Virginia Beach CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Hodges, Y. M. (Mecklenburg), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Hoffman, E. Murphy (Culpeper County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Hogan, Martin L. (Bureau of Teaching Materials), 1943-1945. (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Holloway, W. J. (Isle of Wight County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Holtzclaw, J. G. (Virginia Electric and Power Company), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Hopkins, A. C., Rev. (Charlotte County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Hopkins, R. C. (Fredericksburg CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Hopper, Robert (Conserve Critical Resources Committee), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Horne, M. L. (Coeburn CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Houston, C. W. (The News Leader), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Howard, John J., 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Hub-Hys - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Howe, E. B., Prof. (Suffolk CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Huffington, Walter (WPID), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Hunt, Raymond (Virginia Public Service Company), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Hunter, Thomas Lomax (King George County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Hunter, W. P. (Roanoke CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Hussey, R. E., Dr. (Virginia Polytechnic Institute), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Hutchison, Ralph C., Dr. (Pennsylvania Council of Defense), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - I - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Jac-Jen - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Jackson, C. V. (Wise County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Jackson, H. F. (Washington County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Jackson, William E. (Charlottesville CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - James, G. L. (Appomattox County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - James, L. D. (Roanoke CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Janeway, Augustine S. (U.S. Office of Civilian Defense), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Jefferson, W. W. (American Red Cross), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Jett-Cranz, Flora, Mrs. (Prince George County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Joh-Jud - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - ,Johnson, A. F. (Millboro CDC) 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Johnson, Nancy K. (Lynchburg CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Jones, Catesby G. (Gloucester County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Jones, Charles M. (Conserve Critical Resources Committee), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Jones, E. B. (Highland County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Jones, John Paul (Onancock Warning Districe), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Jones, R. F. (Chesterfield County Farm Demonstration Agent), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - ,Jones, R. J. (Pittsylvania County CDC) 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Jones, S. J. (Buckingham County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Jordan, Harry B., Lt. Col. (Virginia District Internal Security Force), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Joyner, M. B. (Dendron CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - K - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Kay, A. W. (Goochland County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Kay, Floyd S. (Bath County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Kaaburg, A. F. (Elizabeth City County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Keay, Roger I., 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Kelly, C. V. (Richmond CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Kelly, Mae, Miss (Charlotte County CDC - Civilian Mobilization), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Kelly, W. Boulton (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Kemp, Verbon E. (State Chamber of Commerce), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Kendig, P. F., Lt. (Office of Naval Intelligence), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Kennard, G. S. (Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Kepler, Lucy V., Miss (University of Illinois Library), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - King, Armin C., Mrs. (Bristol CDC - Civilian Mobilization), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - King, Marshall (Fredericksburg CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - King, Percy C. (Surry County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - Kraisel, Frederick, Jr., Lt. Col. (U.S. Office of Civilian Defense - Industrial Protection), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Kreh, Lewis, Maj. (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1943-1945. (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - Lab-Lay - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Lambdin, A. L. (Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Lambert, R. L. (Richlands CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Lancaster, Dabney S. (State Dept. of Education), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Landis, James M. (Galax CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Landreth, S. F. (Galax CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Lane, H. M. (Campbell County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Lanham, Catherine (Office of War Information), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Larrick, H. R. (Clifton Forge CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Laughon, Fred T. (Warren County CDC - Civilian Mobilization), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Lea-Lez - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Lee, C. C. (Franklin County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Lee, Dudley (Alexandria CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Lee, Robert T. (Stafford County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Legendre, Leonce R., Lt. Col. (Washington Civilian Defense Region), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Lemay, E. W. (General Outdoor Advertising Company), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Lemley, G. M. (Frederick County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Lenroot, Katherine F. (U.S. Dept. of Labor - Children's Bureau), 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Leonard Embroidery Company, 1943-1945. (Box 22, Folder 19)